What the hell...
...is going on here?
Welcome, Kizuna.
Mom...
Episode 11
Operation Take Back Tokyo -Apocalypse-
What's going on here?!
Tokyo was supposed to be destroyed!
How is it back to normal?!
It's not back to normal at all.
What...?
What you saw
was an illusion created by magic.
A reflection of what once was.
Why would you do that?!
This city is a Plant of sorts.
I've excluded only you
from the effects of the magic field
covering this area.
They're seeing an illusion of peaceful days.
That allows me to efficiently and continually
harvest their life energy.
The field absorbs the life energy,
turns it into magical energy,
and then sends it to Batlantis.
It's a small area for now,
but soon it will cover all of Tokyo.
Then all of Japan.
And eventually the whole world
will become a Plant.
What...
What the hell do you think
their lives are?
You're always like this.
You only see everything as a subject
for your experiments!
Me, Sis, Amaterasu...
I'm taking you back with me!
I'll make you tell me a way
to safely remove the Heart Hybrid Cores!
It's impossible.
Those things
are out of place artifacts
even in the other world.
I simply used the cores
to create a system that
would let a normal person
produce life energy as a
replacement for magical energy.
You didn't make them?
I did not.
Th-Then how can they be removed?
I just told you it was impossible.
Shut up!
Everyone... They're all...
They're all going to die!
Every last one of them!
All humans die, right?
Damn you!
That's enough.
I will be your opponent now.
Get ready!
I can't fight here.
I can't get the people of Tokyo
caught up in this.
You don't think I'll let you
get away, do you?!
Everything's going
according to plan, isn't it?
Let us go as well.
Yes, Nayuta-sama.
No—!
Come...
Amaterasu!
Come get some.
I'll send you all to heaven.
You look like you'll entertain me.
Everyone...
Let's do this!
Right!
This is the Entrance sealing team.
We're in the Yamanote Line area.
Roger.
Continue the mission.
Magitech signals to the northeast!
What?
They found us?
Everyone, stay alert!
Work teams, get to it!
We'll defend this place to the death!
That big one's tough.
Those two were powerless against it...
I'll leave them to Kizuna,
and buy some time!
Okay, here we go, fatass!
She disappeared?
Too slow!
Don't get cocky!
Aine!
Are you okay, Aine?
Hang in there!
Just wait! I'll—
I told you I wouldn't let you get away.
The girl I'll take back.
But the rest of you are apparently useless,
so I'll eliminate you all.
If I only had...
...strength...
What?!
I'm sorry I'm late, Captain!
Sylvia!
Is that your...?
Yes!
This is my Heart Hybrid Gear,
Taros!
Taros?
Leave this to me!
Hurry up!
Okay.
But don't take any big risks!
That's an order!
Roger!
Sorry, Sylvia.
How dare you...
how dare you...
How dare you do that to me?!
I'll protect everyone!
I won't let you lay another finger on them!
Intercept!
Hit her!
I won't...
...lose to someone like this!
Someone like this...
I won't lose!
I won't lose, either!
Impact!
Begone from this place!
Wow...
What power...
That is... Taros...
I lost?
Me?
That's impossible. Me?
A member of the Royal Guards?
To someone like her?
No, that can't be!
I'd rather die than lose to a Lemurian.
That's right.
I'll die!
What are you going to do?!
Shut up!
This is your fault!
For doing this to me... To me!
So it's all over!
For you!
For your friends!
Everything!
Everything! Everything!
I'll blow it all away!
No!
Inferno!
I won't let you!
No!
The energy ball that appeared
has a calorific value of
7.2 exa-high-mega-joules!
And it's still rising!
Not only will it wipe out Tokyo,
it will destroy all of the Kanto region!
I'm blocking it with my shield,
but it's still hot!
Are you okay, Sylvia?!
Captain!
I'm coming!
No, don't!
Your shields probably can't handle it!
But the people of Tokyo...
I'll use my Immoral Weapon.
What?
Wait, Sylvia!
Connection Failed
Leave it to me!
Sylvia!
Shield generator, full drive!
Immoral Weapon:
Titania!
Full Power
Ignition Impact!
Sylvia!
Are you okay?
Captain...
Did I protect everyone?
Yeah.
You did great, Sylvia!
Enough power to create a black hole...
That was quite the splendid sight.
Let us meet again,
Kizuna.
They just keep coming.
But our Counts...
They're coming this way!
They won't give us a chance to resupply?
I thought this might happen,
so I already took measures.
Something's coming!
What?
What is that?
A mid-range ballistic-type supply room.
AKA The Bullet Love Room.
Start with the ones whose
Counts are the lowest.
The others are to provide
as much support as possible.
Roger.
Okay, we'll start with Himekawa.
R-Right!
The others are to provide support!
Roger.
Aine, Sylvia!
Let's clear out the small fry!
You got it!
No, don't!
What's going on here?
Don't worry.
They're just having a wonderful dream.
Who's there?
You!
She disappeared?
Now, Lemurian,
what is your dream?
What is wrong with me?
Not there... No!
What am I doing?
At a time like this...
I can't concentrate?!
Because I don't have any strength?
Fighting was all I had!
But now I'm like this.
I want power so that I can stay myself!
I'll finish it now!
Take this!
No!
You're finally out.
Yurishia!
Your Heart Hybrid always
takes so long, Hayuru.
Well, you were having a good time, I suppose.
Th-That's crass slander!
I would never do something
as perverted as this...
...b-because I wanted to!
Okay, okay, I get it.
Anyway, now that you've recharged,
get to work.
Of course!
Neros!
See you.
Aine!
Aine?
A-Aine-san? What do you think you're doing?
It's supposed to be my turn next!
No fair, Aine!
Talk about an annoying crowd.
Aine?
Kizuna, do it with me right now.
Huh? But your Hybrid Count is still high.
To change the course of
this battle, I want...
...the forbidden weapon.
But that's...
Don't worry, Kizuna.
I am who I am.
No matter what happens, that won't change.
So do it with me...
Let's Climax Hybrid.
All right.
I'll take you someplace special.
Illustration: Hiroyuki Yoshikawa
Aine, ever since we met that day,
I think I knew.
That I was here to protect you!
Me, too. I was able to feel it...
Next time: Aine -Aines-
...because I met you.
I'm not scared of anything anymore, Kizuna.